Shivam Srivastava

Shivamsrivastava8355@gmail.com

7905782625

linkedin.com/in/shivam-srivastava-994898214

Summary

I have total more then 4+ year experience in HR ,bank and Retail. I am expertise in Recruitment and Hiring ,Training and Development, Maintain Company Culture. Manage Employee Benefits, Create a Safe Work Environment, Sales target achievement , maintain employees strength , timing for work , quick problem resolver , I have good knowledge of managing office and employees . I very dedicated for my work .

Experience

Human Resources Executive

Copperchips

May 2022 - Present (4 months +)

Filed paperwork, sorted and delivered mail and maintained office organization.

Delivered friendly assistance with new hires throughout interviewing and hiring process.

Posted positions through approved recruitment channels.

Coordinated itineraries and scheduled appointments for human resources staff.

Processed employee termination paperwork at direction of supervisory staff.

Organized new employee orientation schedules for new hires.

Assistant Manager

Kotak Mahindra Bank

Nov 2021 - May 2022 (7 months)

Developed loyal and highly satisfied customer base through proactive management of team customer service strategies.

Recognized staff for contributions to company success to foster engagement and increase productivity.

Conducted weekly staff meetings to motivate staff members, address concerns and questions, plan improvements and evaluate progress toward goals.

Introduced new products or services, increased marketing activities and improved customer service to drive sales.

Increased employee performance and job satisfaction to strengthen retention and engagement.

Developed strategy to increase sales and drive profits.

Refance Sales Team Leader

Reliance Retail

Sep 2018 - Nov 2021 (3 years 3 months)

Ensure High sales and service quality at floor.

Maximizing high value product contribution in Sales.

Resolving customer quaries and complaints.

Ensure SOP adherence at floor.

Prepare marketing strategies and plan for BTL activities.

Brand Promotion.

Marketting and leading team for identified catchments.

Education

Swami Vivekananda Subharti University, Meerut

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Human Resources Management/Personnel Administration, General Aug 2017 - Nov 2019



🗽 Deendayal Upadhyay Gorakhpur University

Bachelor's degree, Sociology Aug 2014 - Oct 2017

Government inter college. deoria

Intermediate, Biology, General Jul 2012 - May 2014

Government inter college

High School Diploma, Maths Jul 2011 - May 2012

Skills

Talent Management • Human Resources Information Systems (HRIS) • Sourcing • Customer Experience • HR Policies • Time Management • Customer Service • Communication • Employee Relations • English